[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma City"]}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "You survived the tornado, then what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I was actually in the south side of Oklahoma City when I'd seen the tornado.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What condition was he in when you were able to physically get to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "He had a couple of ribs broken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "ORGAN: And Jerrel, who is this man, do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerrel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "And do you know if they're extending the same principle to other people who may have been in your position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "ALEY: I believe so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Can we see it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "How bad have we landed you in it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Is it set right there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Alain"]}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "And what's your -- what's your name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "My name is Michelle Alain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "How are you all doing as a family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "We are doing wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 217, "question": "What was it like for you, Jordan, to actually experience a tornado that big?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "It was just --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jordan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Did you fear at one stage that you may not all come out alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, before, you know -- before the tornado hit, I could tell by just looking at it from how close it was that this is not the kind of tornado or storm that you want to be above ground for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "And they saw the car in the picture and posted it on Facebook, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Yes, they were taking random pictures of the storm debris, and things, and inside one of these pictures she happened to notice the vehicle that we had described.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Is that your understanding, Congressman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RBS", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Why is that, and what will happen in light of what's happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, most of the newer schools actually do have safe rooms in them that are added automatically.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What has it been like on the ground there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "It's -- thank you, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["OU"]}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What are you doing for accommodations for your family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, thank the Lord, OU is supplying housing here for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Norman", "Lindsey", "Jeremiah"], "TIME": ["yesterday morning"]}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What was your reaction, RJ, when you realized that Phoebe had survived after you had given up all hope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I was -- I had gone to Norman yesterday morning while Lindsey and Jeremiah were out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "But you believe that it must have traveled through the air for up to 40 or 50 acres, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "TO", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I don't know how far it came.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "What did you think when you saw this horse, standing there alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "EX", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Honestly, I just quickly saw it, and my mission was to get the kids out and to look to assess what injuries we had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "How are they all doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "They're all doing well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "What happened to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I have a cracked rib and some stitches on my back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "How are you feeling about it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I am still shaken up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "It was -- it was amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "The people who have lost loved ones in Oklahoma, particularly ones who have lost their kids and so on, what is the best advice that you've learned, maybe for yourself, that you could offer them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Well, the most valuable thing you have in the world is your memory.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma"]}}]